ILR School ILR Press Records /4127
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School ILR Press Records
1970-1989
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4127
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
7994516
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 24, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3001: Jean T. McKelvey Papers /3012: Alice Cook Papers /3069: ILR School Scrapbook /4100: ILR School Dean's Office "Report of the ILR Review Panel" Background Documentation /4117 P: ILR School Photographs /4158: John P. Windmuller Additional Papers /4164: Harrison M. Trice Additional Papers /4170: J. Gormly Miller Additional Papers /4191 AV: ILR School Audio-Visual Department Video Cassette Collection /4219: Martin P. Catherwood Library Administrative Office Additional Files /4232: James A. Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files /4236 PUBS: Vernon Briggs Publications /4256: ILR Press Article Reprints and Promotional Materials /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files 6347 PUBS: 1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Publications
ILR Press; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
7994516
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum Volume 10.1-10.2, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum Volume 10.3-10.4, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum Volume 11.1-11.2, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum Volume 11.3-13.3, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum Volume 14.2-15.2, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ILR Reprints No. 494-509, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ILR Reprints No. 510-521, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ILR Reprints No. 522-540, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ILR Reprints No. 541-570, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ILR Reprints No. 571-581, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ILR Reprints No. 582-621, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ILR Reprints No. 622-633, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ILR Reprints No. 335-349, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ILR Reprints No. 350-363, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ILR Reprints No. 364-374, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ILR Reprint Series No. 375-387, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ILR Reprint Series No. 388-402, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ILR Reprint Series No. 403-416, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- ILR Reprint Series No. 417-431, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- ILR Reprint Series No. 432-449, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- ILR Reprint Series No. 450-467, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- ILR Reprint Series No. 468-478, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- ILR Reprint Series No. 479-493, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ILR Reprints No. 526-548, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- ILR Reprints No. 549-556, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- ILR Reprints No. 557-564, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ILR Reprints No. 565-587, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- ILR Reprints No. 587-594, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- ILR Reprints No. 594-603, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- ILR Reprints No. 604-613, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- ILR Reprints No. 614-624, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)